<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Path Creation</string>


    <!-- to toggle the open close button of the navigation drawer -->
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>

    <string name="nav_notification">Notification</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="about_writing"> <br><b>Path Creation Academy is an innovative educational application that
        helps learners of all ages and backgrounds to discover their passions, develop new skills, and create
        their own unique paths in life.\n</b></br>

        <br>\n</br>

        <br>At its core, Path Creation Academy is a platform that provides a variety of learning opportunities,
            including courses, workshops, tutorials, and resources, that are designed to empower learners to
            pursue their interests and achieve their goals. The app offers a diverse range of content, including
            topics such as entrepreneurship, creative arts, technology, personal development, and more.\n</br>

        <br>\n</br>

        <br>One of the key features of Path Creation Academy is its personalized learning approach. The app
            allows learners to create their own learning paths, choose their own pace, and explore different
            topics according to their interests and needs. This flexibility and customization enable learners
            to stay motivated and engaged while learning at their own pace.\n</br>

        <br>\n</br>

        <br>The app also offers a variety of interactive tools and resources, such as quizzes, assessments,
            and feedback mechanisms, to help learners track their progress, identify areas for improvement, and
            receive constructive feedback from their peers and instructors. Additionally, the app provides
            learners with access to a supportive community of fellow learners, mentors, and experts who can
            offer guidance, support, and networking opportunities.\n</br>

        <br>\n</br>

        <br>Overall, Path Creation Academy is a powerful educational tool that empowers learners to discover
            their passions, develop new skills, and create their own paths in life. Whether you are a student,
            a professional, or someone looking to explore new opportunities, Path Creation Academy has something
            to offer for everyone.\n</br>

        <br>\n</br>

    </string>



    <string-array name="sound_options">
        <item>Option 1</item>
        <item>Option 2</item>
        <item>Option 3</item>
        <item>Option 4</item>
        <!-- Add more sound options as needed -->
    </string-array>
</resources>